readinga-z.com 2013-08-11

# Learning A-Z Privacy Statement | Learning A-Z Help

Learning A-Z obeys a strict code of privacy in regards to the information collected for customers and visitors to any Learning A-Z website: Reading A-Z, Raz-Kids, Reading-Tutors, Vocabulary A-Z, and Writing A-Z. The following outlines what information we collect, what we do with it, and how you can determine how information about you is used. 

**Information Collection and Use:** Learning A-Z is the sole owner of the information collected on its website. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Learning A-Z collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

Learning A-Z websites are directed at adults and educators, and with the exception of Raz-Kids, are not directed to children under the age of 13. All Learning A-Z websites, including Raz-Kids, operate in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. Learning A-Z will not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from anyone under 13 years of age. 

**Registration:** If you wish to download materials or resources, make a purchase, participate in a contest, or receive information, we will ask you to register. During registration you will be required to provide your contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the services on our websites for which you have expressed interest. 

**Subscribe:** We request information from you on our order form. During subscription registration you may be required to provide your contact information (such as name and email address), and how you would like to pay for your subscription (credit card, check, purchase order, etc.). 

**Cookies:** Learning A-Z websites use cookies to create a more enjoyable user experience. A cookie is a small data file that websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. Cookies allow our websites to remember important information about you that makes your use of our website a more satisfying experience. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our website. In many ways, cookies have become a way of life on the Web. Their use is now an accepted industry practice and is common among most of the major Internet websites. You can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, or even to decline cookies from websites on the Internet. However, if a user rejects cookies on a Learning A-Z website, login and use of the website cannot be enabled. 

**Log Files:** We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the website, track users movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

**Sharing:** We do not share aggregated demographic information with anyone. We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

**Surveys & Contests: **From time to time, we request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary, and you have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of Learning A-Z websites. 

**Security:** Learning A-Z takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information, that information is encrypted. 

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. 

Learning A-Z does not store credit card information in our database. This is to both reduce our liability and protect your interests. 

If you have any questions about the security at any Learning A-Z website, or the order process, please email [ support@learninga-z.com](mailto:support@learninga-z.com). 

Notification of Changes: If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes each Learning A-Z website home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a chance to inform us not to use their information in a different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy in place when the information was collected.
